{
    "subject": "resource/Red_Rock_West",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "John Dahl",
    "human_readable": "John Dahl wrote Red Rock West.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.856116533279419,
            "question": "Who wrote the movie Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5741868019104004,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie written by John Dahl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4809102416038513,
            "question": "Can you name another movie written by John Dahl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46732452511787415,
            "question": "Is John Dahl known for writing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.465745210647583,
            "question": "What might the plot of Red Rock West be about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4344891309738159,
            "question": "Where might one find information about the production of Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42648249864578247,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did Red Rock West receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42451348900794983,
            "question": "What genre is Red Rock West likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3845518231391907,
            "question": "When was Red Rock West likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1627950519323349,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for starring in John Dahl's movies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Dahl wrote Red Rock West.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6565_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Red Rock West likely released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6565_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Red Rock West likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6565_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards or recognition did Red Rock West receive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6565_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6565_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I found that:\n\n* The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6565/re-ranker-msmarco/94.txt mentions John Dahl as the director of Red Rock West, but not as the author.\n* The same document mentions \"Directed and co-written by John Dahl\" which suggests that he wrote part of the screenplay for Red Rock West.\n\nGiven this information, I would say that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the screenplay for Red Rock West was written by John Dahl and his brother Rick Dahl, which supports the triple \"John Dahl wrote Red Rock West.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The screenplay for Red Rock West was written by John Dahl and Rick Dahl.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}